question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {
        "category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The 'Gympie Stinger' is the deadliest plant in the world.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Type 1 diabetes is a result of the liver working improperly.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Anatomy considers the forms of macroscopic structures such as organs and organ systems.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The chemical element Lithium is named after the country of Lithuania.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Sugar contains fat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A plant that has a life cycle for more than a year is known as an annual.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "'Tachycardia' or 'Tachyarrhythmia' refers to a resting heart-rate near or over 100 BPM.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
